What's up everybody? This is Cortland from AndyHackers.com and you're listening
to the
Andy Hackers podcast. More people than ever are building cool stuff online and
making
a lot of money in the process. And on this show, I sit down with these Andy
Hackers to
discuss the ideas, the opportunities and the strategies they're taking advantage
of so
the rest of us can do the same.
I'm here with Justin Jackson, the founder of Transistor, which is a very
successful podcast
hosting company. It's what I'm using to host this podcast and also my other
podcast brains.
Justin, welcome back to Andy Hackers. I think this is your third time on the
show.
Yeah. Well, it's good. It's just good to chat with you. It's actually good to
chat with
any human being these days.
Yeah. Well, you're particularly fun to talk to you because it's very easy to
talk to.
We have our Twitter DMs back and forth where we share random thoughts on stuff,
but it's
good to just flow.
Yeah, totally. I've noticed the change in the way you do the show. When I
listen, it's
become a lot more conversational.
Yeah. Well, it's much more fun to have authentic, normal conversations. And
there's this idea
of a... You're familiar with the concept of an overton window. It's kind of
like, what
are you allowed to say? What are you not allowed to say? There's kind of like,
impolite society.
There's just balance on things that everybody agrees are okay and everybody
doesn't agree
are okay.
And I think if you have a show or an audience, Twitter account, newsletter or
whatever, you
kind of create your own overton window, meaning that whatever it is that you put
out, the
people who like it will stick with you and the people who don't won't. And so
you can
kind of do whatever you want on your own show. But once you pick something,
you're kind of
locked into it because now your audience wants that. And so it's always kind of
hard to change
the format of a podcast show because it's like, if I've been doing interviews
for a long
time and then I'm like, you know what? I want to do more conversational stuff. A
lot of
people will be like, what the hell? What happened to the interviews?
Yeah. What an interesting idea. Like what's Bon Jovi's overton window? It's
like, everyone
wants to hear the same songs over and over again. They don't want anything new,
right?
You get locked in.
Yeah. Yeah. And this is a real actual, this is a fundamental challenge of life,
which is I do
think people need to grow, businesses need to grow and change and adapt. And
people don't
like change. But if you don't change, you kind of, you can recede, you know, you
can, your
business can die over time just because it becomes gradually more irrelevant or
doesn't
respond to current market conditions. And then you as a person, you know, you
might